Hey there, curious minds! Ever
heard of the eerie catacombs
beneath Paris? Well, beneath the
buzzing city streets lies a
silent maze of tunnels with
a spine-chilling history. These catacombs
hold the remains of over
six million people. That's right,
six million. They were created
in the late 18th century
to tackle the issue of
overcrowded cemeteries that were causing
serious health issues. Now, that
meant transferring bones from these
overflowing graveyards covertly at night
to avoid public panic and
outrage. And here's where it
gets really bizarre. Some of
these old tunnels have been
forgotten with time, leading to
legends of people wandering in,
and never finding their way
out. What's more, during World
War II, the French resistance
used these tunnels to hide
from the Nazis, who, by
the way, also built their
own bunkers down there. So
next time you're walking the
romantic streets of Paris, just
remember the haunting history that
lies just beneath your feet.